First of all, thank you for these people standing behind me who, like the ones in front,
give them here, Lord, they help all of them in moments when they take some water and just
tie it.
And, you know, I just created you give them strength to go on and wisdom, what to do.
Lord, I thank you for the privilege we have of living here and that these make decisions
to help it be better for us, let them look at decisions and not just be very effective
and wise.
Jesus, amen.
Yes.
Amen.
Unfortunately, it is to the fact that the United States of America and to the Republic for which
you say, one nation under God and in the visible liberty and justice for all.
Thank you, Leon, for the very appropriate, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very
good.
It changes size depending upon what.
Four.
I told you to input on the schedule of personal experiences.
Five.
Five A claims list.
Most two proof.
Take it.
Hi.
Barnes.
5B.
Management.
December 16, 2025.
Regular meeting.
Motion to proof.
Sorry.
So, Barnes.
Hi.
5C.
Tetra Tech claim from Pensacola.
G-R-D-A.
This is the engineering for the G-R-D-A lawsuit.
This is, they kind of ran some models for Miss United.
I showed us some different things for the civil litigation that we went through.
So, if this is approved tonight, it will be remaining a balance of $695,716.80 of the $750,000
that we budgeted for the year.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
ansen.
Is the red.
Six.
Jaunus May.
7th.
приехat же an assessment.
Hey.
Chu BRt.
Yes.
A cab.
Tumen.
I have one thing in front of you on the diocese we have public notice that would be going out tomorrow.
or GRD, it raised R rates back in October, November.
And so then ours will go into effect January this month.
So we'll be sending these out in a mailing
will be met up tomorrow from Tulsa.
Thanks.
So just for clarity, Tyler, when we talk about the first one,
E1 residential customer charge currently $15.45,
that's going up $4.
Yes, but if you remember, that is paying for our match
for the AMI.
That's like the AMI for the customer's going to see a $4.
Customer charging increase and then I was it $0.50 per KWH.
It's $0.50, didn't it?
Or is it $0.50?
Well, yeah, it has to be $0.50, doesn't it, right?
So just wanted to clarify that so people understand.
So if you remember, the grant that we got for AMI
because I know it's been a year and a half ago or whatever,
it was like, we have to have come up with a match.
So this is how we could afford to do our match.
We'll just do that.
Which to me having a portal that you can log into
and look at your usage is, will be very neat.
So just making everybody aware,
we'll also wanted to also push it out in a couple of days
to let everybody know too that it's going to be in their flyer.
So this will be separate.
And then there are bills because I know we've got compliance
people like, well, we don't read our bill.
We just get it and tear it up though on the mail.
So we're sending it out separate to try something different.
So that's all I have.
Now in this meeting, we'll be continuing from the Council
Chamber to remain in the staff room for the purpose of the
executive session as a completion of the regular meeting
for the MIPFA.